

Full-stack engineer with over 7 years of experience in web development, managing all aspects of the development process. Worked on 20+ projects and solved complex business problems in various industries including marketing, healthcare, and eCommerce. Consistently saved costs while increasing profits. I'm Ready for an opportunity to use my skills to grow your revenue exponentially.

SASHA SAMOYLOV

Address:

Vozdvizhenka Street, 10, Moscow, Russia

E-Mail:

sasha.samoylov@gmail.com

Skype:

live:.cid.e07bcb612fe88d1b

Skills

- JavaScript
- JQuery
- PHP
- SQL
- HTML
- CSS
- React
- Angular
- Node.js
- Express.js
- Python
- Mongodb

Skill Highlights

- High speed communication
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Innovative
- Service-focused

Experience

09/2019 to present

Senior Full-Stack Developer - BRANDSMARKTE, Moscow, Russia

- Implemented enhancements that improved web functionality and responsiveness.
- Work closely with programmers and clients to meet project requirements, goals, and desired functionality.
- Maintain optimal workflow.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.

05/2015 to 09/2019

Senior Full-Stack Developer - WEBSAILORS.PRO, Taganrog, Russia

- Produced the functional, attractive, scalable web applications using a combination of JavaScript and other web technologies.
- Worked cooperatively with other programmers and designers.
- Tested code, tracked and fixed bugs as needed.
- Created and/or modify the graphic elements as needed.
- Evaluated the impact of change requests and provided management with estimates of the time and effort to implement the changes.

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science-2014
BAUMAN MOSCOW STATE TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY, Moscow,
2012 - 2015

- Excelled in UI/UX to create user friendly websites
- Pursued the knowledge in web services